<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on him.happyhippos</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on him.happyhippos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 00:02:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter experiences</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2016-02-16-winter-experiences/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 00:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2016-02-16-winter-experiences/</guid>
      <description>Part of being a parent is being able to share the things that you find joy in doing, and this past week I got a chance to help my daughter discover the wonders of winter. On Thursday, we went skating with the Grad Cell small group, and she had a blast! She didn&amp;#8217;t end up skating on her own at all, so we had to take turns holding her up as she walked around the ice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unbiased</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-12-30-unbiased/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 10:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-12-30-unbiased/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve been having an ongoing dispute with my wife about how cute our daughter is. She insists that I am asking biased questions when I try to get opinions on how she compares to other babies. Well, this past week, I went to make a reservation at a local Chinese restaurant that we frequent, and this is the conversation that ensued:
Me: Hi, I&amp;#8217;d like to make a reservation for six adults and one baby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grammar wars</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-10-17-grammar-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 13:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-10-17-grammar-wars/</guid>
      <description>I was forced to take a mandatory course yesterday as part of my employment duties. I got about halfway through the course before I nearly broke down in frustration at the lack of basic grammar and editing in the questions and content. I was chatting with a co-worker while I was doing the course, and expressed my anger to her. She told me to &amp;#8220;turn your internal grammar/spelling/logic sensor off&amp;#8221;. Since there was no off switch for my sensor, I resorted to documenting the atrocities against the English language that I was witnessing as a way of dealing with the fact that I had to read these unedited words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our little bean got her first piece of mail today&amp;#8230;</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-08-13-our-little-bean-got-her-first-piece-of-mail-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 23:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-08-13-our-little-bean-got-her-first-piece-of-mail-today/</guid>
      <description>and her first dress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy One Week Birthday, Little bean!</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-07-29-happy-one-week-birthday-lb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 13:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-07-29-happy-one-week-birthday-lb/</guid>
      <description>In your honour, and with your help, I&amp;#8217;ve created this video of you.
You&amp;#8217;re going to have a great time growing up, I can already tell!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timeline Part 2</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-07-27-224/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 18:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-07-27-224/</guid>
      <description>See Part 1 if you&amp;#8217;re looking for what happened before.
3:07 &amp;#8211; I park my car illegally. Midwives reassure me that &amp;#8220;they don&amp;#8217;t ticket at night&amp;#8221;.
3:10 &amp;#8211; We get into the labour room. Wifey&amp;#8217;s still having some pretty rough contractions (obviously). Baby&amp;#8217;s not moving much.
3:35 &amp;#8211; Gynecologist stops by, briefly. She&amp;#8217;s got crazy red lips, and wifey tells me she looks like a vampire. Puts on a front cover apron and goggles, but parts of her face are uncovered (will be relevant later).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timeline</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-07-25-timeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 03:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-07-25-timeline/</guid>
      <description>July 21, 2013
05:00 &amp;#8211; She starts feeling contractions, and she thinks they&amp;#8217;re Braxton Hicks contractions. They come every 4-5 minutes, and last for a short while. She takes some gravol and tylenol, and goes back to sleep.
08:45 &amp;#8211; My alarm goes off for church &amp;#8211; I&amp;#8217;m supposed to lead worship. Wifey says she can&amp;#8217;t make church, so I decide to stay at home with her (Sorry Chris!). We let Pastor Tim know that we can&amp;#8217;t make it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stolen food&amp;#8230; and other things</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-04-19-stolen-food-and-other-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 12:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-04-19-stolen-food-and-other-things/</guid>
      <description>This is getting ridiculous. A few weeks ago, I went on vacation for 4 days to Vancouver, and I came back to a chair that had a broken armrest and covered in dog hair. Then, last week, my craked green plate disappeared from my desk. Now, today, the last straw! My loving wife made me some delicious lemon squares based on crushed macadamia nut crust, and today I came in to eat it&amp;#8230; and it was GONE!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Lunch</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-03-15-stolen-lunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 13:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-03-15-stolen-lunch/</guid>
      <description>I am still in shock (mostly from hunger) that someone stole my lunch at work today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Board games</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-01-15-board-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 05:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-01-15-board-games/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;#8217;ve known me for any amount of time, you know that I&amp;#8217;m a pretty huge fan of board games. Whenever we host almost anyone, the conversation almost inevitably turns to my giant cabinet filled with games. What is it about games that I enjoy so much? Part of it is the mental challenge of identifying the best line of play is. Another part is the fact that the options are limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skyfall</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-01-09-skyfall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2013 04:06:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-01-09-skyfall/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s been awhile since I&amp;#8217;ve posted&amp;#8230; a long while. In fact, this whole site has been down, and I haven&amp;#8217;t bothered to put it back up again&amp;#8230; until now. It was a pretty interesting coincidence that my first post on this resurrected site is about the date I just had with my wife, watching a movie that contrasts the weathered wisdom of the past with the impetuous immediacy of youth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>carpal tunnel</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-01-29-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2003 09:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-01-29-1/</guid>
      <description>Alright, I&amp;#8217;ve just discovered that I have carpal tunnel syndrome.. Yay! =P I checked the symptoms, and I have ALL of them&amp;#8230; numbness, pain, and difficulty grasping objects. So now I installed a program called Break Reminder that will force me to take a 20 second break every 10 minutes. It&amp;#8217;s a pretty robust program, and I&amp;#8217;m quite enchanted with it. =) I think I&amp;#8217;ll install it at work. Anyhow, it&amp;#8217;s time for lunch!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>