<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on him.happyhippos</title>
    <link>http://example.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on him.happyhippos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 00:02:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter experiences</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2016-02-16-winter-experiences/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 00:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2016-02-16-winter-experiences/</guid>
      <description>Part of being a parent is being able to share the things that you find joy in doing, and this past week I got a chance to help my daughter discover the wonders of winter. On Thursday, we went skating with the Grad Cell small group, and she had a blast! She didn&amp;#8217;t end up skating on her own at all, so we had to take turns holding her up as she walked around the ice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best places (we&amp;#8217;ve found) to eat in KWC</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2016-01-20-best-places-weve-found-to-eat-in-kw/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 17:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2016-01-20-best-places-weve-found-to-eat-in-kw/</guid>
      <description>Comfort food
Crazy Canuck
Crossroads Family Restaurant
Hog&amp;#8217;s Tail &amp;#8211; get the Chicken and Waffles
SOS BBQ &amp;#8211; amazing fish and chips!
Frites
Pierogies
The Village Eatery
Asian
Kinkaku
Mikey&amp;#8217;s Eatery (toast and milk tea and sesame chicken)
Bogda
Foodie Fruitie &amp;#8211; GREAT ramen!
Fine(ish) dining
Fork and Cork
Del&amp;#8217;s Enoteca
Borealis
Langdon Hall
Dessert and Drinks
Noon Moment
Sugar Marmalade</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unbiased</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-12-30-unbiased/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 10:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-12-30-unbiased/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve been having an ongoing dispute with my wife about how cute our daughter is. She insists that I am asking biased questions when I try to get opinions on how she compares to other babies. Well, this past week, I went to make a reservation at a local Chinese restaurant that we frequent, and this is the conversation that ensued:
Me: Hi, I&amp;#8217;d like to make a reservation for six adults and one baby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grammar wars</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-10-17-grammar-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2013 13:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-10-17-grammar-wars/</guid>
      <description>I was forced to take a mandatory course yesterday as part of my employment duties. I got about halfway through the course before I nearly broke down in frustration at the lack of basic grammar and editing in the questions and content. I was chatting with a co-worker while I was doing the course, and expressed my anger to her. She told me to &amp;#8220;turn your internal grammar/spelling/logic sensor off&amp;#8221;. Since there was no off switch for my sensor, I resorted to documenting the atrocities against the English language that I was witnessing as a way of dealing with the fact that I had to read these unedited words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our little bean got her first piece of mail today&amp;#8230;</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-08-13-our-little-bean-got-her-first-piece-of-mail-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2013 23:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-08-13-our-little-bean-got-her-first-piece-of-mail-today/</guid>
      <description>and her first dress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy One Week Birthday, Little bean!</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-07-29-happy-one-week-birthday-lb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2013 13:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-07-29-happy-one-week-birthday-lb/</guid>
      <description>In your honour, and with your help, I&amp;#8217;ve created this video of you.
You&amp;#8217;re going to have a great time growing up, I can already tell!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timeline Part 2</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-07-27-224/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 18:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-07-27-224/</guid>
      <description>See Part 1 if you&amp;#8217;re looking for what happened before.
3:07 &amp;#8211; I park my car illegally. Midwives reassure me that &amp;#8220;they don&amp;#8217;t ticket at night&amp;#8221;.
3:10 &amp;#8211; We get into the labour room. Wifey&amp;#8217;s still having some pretty rough contractions (obviously). Baby&amp;#8217;s not moving much.
3:35 &amp;#8211; Gynecologist stops by, briefly. She&amp;#8217;s got crazy red lips, and wifey tells me she looks like a vampire. Puts on a front cover apron and goggles, but parts of her face are uncovered (will be relevant later).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Timeline</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-07-25-timeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 03:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-07-25-timeline/</guid>
      <description>July 21, 2013
05:00 &amp;#8211; She starts feeling contractions, and she thinks they&amp;#8217;re Braxton Hicks contractions. They come every 4-5 minutes, and last for a short while. She takes some gravol and tylenol, and goes back to sleep.
08:45 &amp;#8211; My alarm goes off for church &amp;#8211; I&amp;#8217;m supposed to lead worship. Wifey says she can&amp;#8217;t make church, so I decide to stay at home with her (Sorry Chris!). We let Pastor Tim know that we can&amp;#8217;t make it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stolen food&amp;#8230; and other things</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-04-19-stolen-food-and-other-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 12:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-04-19-stolen-food-and-other-things/</guid>
      <description>This is getting ridiculous. A few weeks ago, I went on vacation for 4 days to Vancouver, and I came back to a chair that had a broken armrest and covered in dog hair. Then, last week, my craked green plate disappeared from my desk. Now, today, the last straw! My loving wife made me some delicious lemon squares based on crushed macadamia nut crust, and today I came in to eat it&amp;#8230; and it was GONE!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Lunch</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-03-15-stolen-lunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 13:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-03-15-stolen-lunch/</guid>
      <description>I am still in shock (mostly from hunger) that someone stole my lunch at work today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Board games</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-01-15-board-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2013 05:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-01-15-board-games/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;#8217;ve known me for any amount of time, you know that I&amp;#8217;m a pretty huge fan of board games. Whenever we host almost anyone, the conversation almost inevitably turns to my giant cabinet filled with games. What is it about games that I enjoy so much? Part of it is the mental challenge of identifying the best line of play is. Another part is the fact that the options are limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skyfall</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2013-01-09-skyfall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2013 04:06:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2013-01-09-skyfall/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s been awhile since I&amp;#8217;ve posted&amp;#8230; a long while. In fact, this whole site has been down, and I haven&amp;#8217;t bothered to put it back up again&amp;#8230; until now. It was a pretty interesting coincidence that my first post on this resurrected site is about the date I just had with my wife, watching a movie that contrasts the weathered wisdom of the past with the impetuous immediacy of youth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Hacking</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2008-08-11-192/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2008 15:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2008-08-11-192/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve recently been reading up on LifeHacker, a blog on getting things done. It&amp;#8217;s all about little tips and tricks for getting things done, both in the digital world, and in the real world. This includes everything from simple tricks like having a desktop background that categorises the different files and folders on your computer desktop, to sites like Hundredpushups.com which is a training program to do one hundred pushups, for anyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citius, Altius, Fortius</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2008-04-21-191/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2008 09:47:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2008-04-21-191/</guid>
      <description>For the first time today, I rollerbladed to work. If you know the area, it&amp;#8217;s quite hilly, and there were a few close calls with the pavement. It was quite intense, and I managed to shave about 6-8 minutes off of my arrival time. I don&amp;#8217;t know if I&amp;#8217;d do it again though. It was getting quite dicey, especially along King St towards Victoria, which are both major intersections. The terrain slopes downhill towards this intersection, and I haven&amp;#8217;t quite mastered the art of slowing down within a narrow strip of sidewalk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>House Mouse</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2008-04-10-190/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2008 22:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2008-04-10-190/</guid>
      <description>So, yesterday, as I was preparing to leave Emily&amp;#8217;s house, we were talking. She was studying in her room, and I was descending the staircase&amp;#8230; when I heard a startled screech. &amp;#8220;There&amp;#8217;s a mouse in my room!&amp;#8221;
Me being the skeptic, I asked her if she was sure she hadn&amp;#8217;t imagined it. After her repeated assurances, I went to investigate. She said it was behind her dresser, so I sealed up all other exits, and shone a flashlight along one side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Origins 2007</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2007-08-26-185/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2007 21:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2007-08-26-185/</guid>
      <description>Origins 2007
Wow, what an experience&amp;#8230; again! It was just as much fun as I remember Gencon being&amp;#8230; only more so, because I have more interests than just board games! It was a shorter drive to Columbus than it was to Indianapolis&amp;#8230; thank goodness, because there were only the two of us going. Got to talk a lot with Richard about guy stuff. Hurrah. =) Anyhow, after leaving at around 3 am, we arrived at 9:45 am without incident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dell&amp;#8230; Why do you tempt me so?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2007-03-20-184/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2007 11:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2007-03-20-184/</guid>
      <description>Another 24&amp;#8243; monitor? For $650?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remembrance Day</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2006-11-10-183/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2006 12:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2006-11-10-183/</guid>
      <description>Almost.
Cheers to a quarter century!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credit Card Fraud</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2006-09-06-180/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2006 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2006-09-06-180/</guid>
      <description>Well, my mom got back from work late yesterday, and when she opened up her credit card statement, she found something amiss&amp;#8230; about $3000 of extra credit card charges for various gasoline stations. After checking her card to make sure she still had it, I told her to call and put a hold on her credit card. To dispute charges, you have to know every line item that you are disputing (obviously).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GenCon Day 3</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2006-08-12-178/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2006 20:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2006-08-12-178/</guid>
      <description>Saturday&amp;#8230; and after two solid days of walking, gaming, and looking at things, I just needed a break. I spent the majority of my time just sitting around and watching the people walk by. I also took the most photos today, as compared to the entire trip. They&amp;#8217;ll be up later, but for now, here are some captions.
Mages!
An entire imperial command, replete with bounty hunters, stormtroopers, and the Dark Lord himself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>google again</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2006-07-14-173/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2006 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2006-07-14-173/</guid>
      <description>Google&amp;#8217;s motto is &amp;#8220;Do No Evil&amp;#8221;. However, their gmail ads leave something to be desired. I was writing out an email to my friends who went camping with me about their final costs. It just so happened that all the campers were chinese. Imagine my suprise when I happen to glance over at the automatically generated sponsored links! Just because we have chinese last names, Google seems to think we want to learn kung fu!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ah, l&amp;#8217;amour est dans le ciel</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2006-02-17-169/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2006 18:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2006-02-17-169/</guid>
      <description>I think spring has come a little earlier this year, with our balmy weather and heavy rains&amp;#8230; and a few newly blossoming relationships. Now, typically relationships don&amp;#8217;t start in the middle of winter when it&amp;#8217;s freezing cold, but the wave of warm weather has possibly given a little nudge to a few budding relationships. =)
I guess I was partially inspired by the rash of relationship articles on Boundless and just a general curiosity inspired by the relationships talk at my Church&amp;#8217;s summer conference to read this book:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ottawa</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2006-02-13-167/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2006 14:19:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2006-02-13-167/</guid>
      <description>Wow, another blog post. I think that I post so infrequently because I tend to write long essays every time I post, and I don&amp;#8217;t often have that much free time to write. Anyway, enough excuses, on to the meat!
 So this past weekend, I went with em to Ottawa for the Winterlude Festival. We both took Friday off, so we could maximise the use of our time, with a smaller fraction of our weekend spent driving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a story of caution (or haxoring microsoft EFS)</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-12-21-166/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2005 22:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-12-21-166/</guid>
      <description>A few days ago, my computer died. Not a huge loss, hard drive intact, and I still have a laptop. Or so I thought.
Anyway, following standard procedure, I immediately hopped on the nearest computer hardware webpage and started drooling over all the latest and greatest hardware of our time. From dual core CPUs to the latest gpu that can render life, the universe, and everything in less than 42 micronanoinfinity seconds, I was all excited about getting my new computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>moving up</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-11-19-165/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2005 00:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-11-19-165/</guid>
      <description>Sigh&amp;#8230; I&amp;#8217;ve just taken the next step in life. Makes me feel old. Hope it&amp;#8217;s worth it. =p</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(I&amp;#8217;m not) Smiling Jack&amp;#8217;s</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-11-01-163/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2005 13:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-11-01-163/</guid>
      <description>My mom decides to use an entertainment book coupon to treat me on the last day they can be used, and the closest restaurant is Smiling Jack&amp;#8217;s, across the street. Our experience was less than stellar. In fact, it was downright terrible. First, the under-dressed waitress kept kept touching my arm to illustrate her points. The food was dry and portions were smaller than a lot of other restaurants we&amp;#8217;ve been to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OOPSLA</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-10-20-162/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2005 11:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-10-20-162/</guid>
      <description>&amp;#8230;ohhhhh&amp;#8230;..
fresh strawberries, watermelon, and pineapples for breakfast every morning&amp;#8230; I think I&amp;#8217;m in heaven&amp;#8230;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&amp;quot;Church&amp;quot;</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-10-16-160/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2005 15:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-10-16-160/</guid>
      <description>This morning, I went to a church down the street from where I&amp;#8217;m staying in San Diego, expecting a Christian church service. Instead, I was shown a mixture of new-age and wiccan philosophies, with the primary theme being that we are all able to do whatever we want, because we are god. Symbols of butterflies and suns were present all through the service. The most disturbing thing was that some of the quotes they used were from the bible or christian sources, but slightly twisted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>covers</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-09-21-159/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2005 17:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-09-21-159/</guid>
      <description>The covers of this book are too far apart. &amp;#8211; Ambrose Bierce
A plethora of newfound free time has left me tackling longer and longer books to keep myself entertained. Sparked by a partial dramatic bedtime reading of a book recently acquired at the Canadian National Exhibition, my newly rediscovered love of science fiction, fantasy, history, punctuation, and essentially any book with pages has caused me to devote a lot of time exploring just how far I can walk without looking up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>maps</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-08-26-158/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2005 11:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-08-26-158/</guid>
      <description>I came to an interesting realisation about myself today&amp;#8230; I love maps! I think it started when I was a child, whenever we&amp;#8217;d go anywhere, I&amp;#8217;d love to follow where we were going on the map. In elementary school, orienteering was my absolute favourite outdoor activity, navigating hazardous (albeit child-safe) terrain with only a map and a compass (and about 20 other classmates doing the same thing). It stemmed partially from my dad&amp;#8217;s career as a driving instructor, I think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new beginnings</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-08-24-157/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2005 16:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-08-24-157/</guid>
      <description>With all the things that are happening in my life, a new job, new relationships, new environment, I decided to release a new version of this site. It&amp;#8217;s cleaner and more intuitive, easier to update and manage. I&amp;#8217;ve fixed a lot of old hacks, and improved the performance a little. Although some of the features have been taken down for maintenance, hopefully the site will be just as easy to read and navigate as always.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>speed boost</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-08-18-156/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2005 15:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-08-18-156/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m in the process of redoing my website, but I figured I&amp;#8217;d trickle some of the technical changes back down to this old blog&amp;#8230; I&amp;#8217;ve been doing some work on my friend&amp;#8217;s website, and because of the challenges of perl, I was forced to write cleaner code without many of the hacks that I did on this site (especially with the comments! I mean seriously, what was I thinking, running a separate query for every weblog on the page to get the comment count?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>small small world</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-07-19-153/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2005 22:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-07-19-153/</guid>
      <description>?????!
So yesterday, I had to take public transit in HK. I was supposed to go to my friend&amp;#8217;s house for dinner, so I dutifully noted the directions she gave me. &amp;#8220;Take the MTR to ??, then get on the 40 or the 40M, or the 23A, 23B, or 23C to the ?????, then get off and walk. The exit in pacific place can lead to the bus stop, or you can find other bus stops around that area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>starlight</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-07-03-152/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2005 14:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-07-03-152/</guid>
      <description>Taken on the flight from beijing.
My first day in beijing can be found here.   Starlight
Starbright
First star I see tonite
Wish I may,
Wish I might
Have the wish I wish tonite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rain, rain, go away..</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-06-30-151/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2005 03:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-06-30-151/</guid>
      <description>I hate rain. I&amp;#8217;m not talking about the once-in-a-while summer storm downpour that clears the air and creates gorgeous rainbows. I&amp;#8217;m talking about the drizzling kind that can make you feel miserable, even after you&amp;#8217;re out of it. For hot weather, once you&amp;#8217;re out if it, in a sheltered place, you&amp;#8217;re okay. Same with cold weather, excluding sunburn and frostbite. But rain clings to your clothes even after you&amp;#8217;re in a dry area, extending the amount of time that you feel gross.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>anticipatory sleeplessness</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-06-19-150/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2005 00:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-06-19-150/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s the night before I leave for hk&amp;#8230; and I can&amp;#8217;t sleep, because I&amp;#8217;ve got SO much on my mind. The last 24 hours have been a blur of activity. From preparing to convo to dining to photographs to packing to flying, it&amp;#8217;s like my life&amp;#8217;s on fast forward. My heartbeat is running pretty high, and I&amp;#8217;m just sitting still, trying to get to bed. I can&amp;#8217;t believe I&amp;#8217;m graduated, too&amp;#8230; that in itself is pretty unbelievable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&amp;quot;flipping&amp;quot;</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-06-09-149/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2005 16:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-06-09-149/</guid>
      <description>My mom has this colourful term for buying and selling rapidly, and I think it comes from real estate. It happens when you buy a house, and then sell it without living in it for a profit. I&amp;#8217;ve been criticised for buying and selling things rapidly, and I actually have my brother a little hooked on rfd, where he&amp;#8217;s a known seller of old electronics. =) Sometimes, I think having an itchy purchase trigger finger (especially for online deals) is a good thing, because no matter what you purchase, usually you can return it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lunch hour</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-05-26-148/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2005 22:39:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-05-26-148/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve been going through my french course, done four or five sample tests, and I need a break, so blogging it is. =p Lunch hour is usually the time when you get to talk to your co-workers about non-work-related things. It&amp;#8217;s kinda like the time where you can bond, and otherwise build friendships. Unfortunately, I&amp;#8217;m in a bit of a dilemma right now&amp;#8230; I don&amp;#8217;t really fit into any of the current &amp;#8220;lunch group cliques&amp;#8221;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflecting on trucks</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-05-24-147/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2005 17:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-05-24-147/</guid>
      <description>J&amp;#8217;ai visitÃ© MontrÃ©al le week-end passÃ©&amp;#8230; il Ã©tais trÃ¨s intÃ©ressant. Although it was raining most of the time, we did get a rainless, albeit cloudy, day on Saturday. The drive up was very long, and I think if I had to visit Montreal in the future, I&amp;#8217;d take le train. By the time we got in, it was close to 1 am. Thanks to Peter for his hospitality and mad tour-guide skills!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>overhaul</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-05-05-145/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2005 10:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-05-05-145/</guid>
      <description>Now that I&amp;#8217;ve started a full time job, it seems that I have more time in the evening. I was talking to a friend the other night though, and post-work energy levels seem to be much lower than post-school energy levels (perhaps because at school there is more to do than sit at a computer all day). Anyway, I&amp;#8217;ve decided that I want to do a (fairly) major overhaul of the site, since it&amp;#8217;s pretty simple right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>button brainstorm</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-05-02-144/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2005 15:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-05-02-144/</guid>
      <description>Why oh why are women&amp;#8217;s shirt buttons backwards? I recently noticed this phenomenon, so I did a little research and this is the information I came up with. To answer this question, we must go back into the ages of antiquity, when men dressed themselves and women didn&amp;#8217;t. Since it was considered bad luck to be left handed, everyone learned to use their right hand. Thus, while men dressed themselves, using their right hands to insert their buttons into the button holes, women were dressed by someone else, having their buttons buttoned by someone in front of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>happenings</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-04-19-143/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2005 13:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-04-19-143/</guid>
      <description>So, finally free! How does it feel? Well, I&amp;#8217;m feeling a bit drained, partially because I slept late, but mostly because I am unsure of where the future goes. That&amp;#8217;s a complicated topic for another time, so lets stick with the easy one of what I did that day. After my exam (which went amazingly well; one of my best yet!) I went to the UW shop sale, picked up some nifty waterloo gear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-03-07-141/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2005 16:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-03-07-141/</guid>
      <description>What a busy weekend! So much packed into those two days.. Big Idea Productions did a few pre-release showings of the new Veggie Tales spectacular Duke and the Great Pie War! It was well done, providing a creative new look into the stories of Ruth and Miriam. Definitely a must see! Also, they gave away $3 off coupons for the dvd and also another dvd, An Easter Carol. Probably going to pick them up at some point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowboarding Lesson Series</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-03-02-139/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2005 00:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-03-02-139/</guid>
      <description>Since I&amp;#8217;ve recently discovered the joy of snowboarding, I thought I&amp;#8217;d post this guide written by my manager. Unfortunately, the guide was so long that I hit the hard limit for my post length. =p So I posted the lessons in reverse order, to be legible. My apologies to my RSS feed readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowboarding Lesson 5: Zen and the Art of Carving</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-03-02-134/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2005 00:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-03-02-134/</guid>
      <description>So. You&amp;#8217;ve tried it a few times, and now you&amp;#8217;re at the level where you can actually make it off the chairlift without wiping out every time. More often than not you make it down the hill without a major wipeout, just a few &amp;#8220;meant to do that&amp;#8221; easily-recoverable touch-and-go&amp;#8217;s. You&amp;#8217;ve ended a snowboarding day without feeling like you&amp;#8217;ve been mugged. Now what? With the ability to control the board against the force of gravity on a snow-and-ice medium, you&amp;#8217;re on that edge between order and chaos that Dick Gabriel was all excited about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>thankful</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-02-18-133/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2005 02:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-02-18-133/</guid>
      <description>Yes, I know, I should be studying or sleeping, but I was reading boundless.org and they had posted a brilliant idea &amp;#8211; Write down ten things you&amp;#8217;re thankful for today. So, here goes:
I&amp;#8217;m thankful for Eric Cheng, sharing part of his delicious dinner with me today.
I&amp;#8217;m thankful for the person sitting next to me during the exam, helping me stress less about it.
I&amp;#8217;m thankful for JT for waking me up this morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>walking on thorns</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-01-25-131/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2005 23:49:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-01-25-131/</guid>
      <description>I just realised something today as I was walking home from school. There is a distinct disadvantage in attending a school that requires so much walking around, especially if your body is not well equipped for such a task. To explain, I&amp;#8217;m going to need some illustrations.
This is a normal foot. The band at the bottom is a tendon that runs along the bottom of your foot, connecting the ball of your foot with the inside rear of your foot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>j.w vs. the mountain, round 2&amp;#8230; FIGHT</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2005-01-05-130/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2005 19:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2005-01-05-130/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m in considerably less pain than last time, which is a good thing, but that is probably in a large part due to the fact that I only went for an hour and a half instead of five hours. The powder was course grit overlaid on ice, so any falls HURT! Getting up hurt too, since my right shoulder and rotator cuff was really tired from activities that I will not mention here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>twilight zone</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-12-31-129/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2004 19:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-12-31-129/</guid>
      <description>I just got up from a 2 hour nap from 4-6 pm&amp;#8230; I had the radio playing in the background, and my dreams went haywire. I dreamed about everything from a new, renovated seagram that looked more like a penthouse than anything else, a huge oil refinery that I had to climb, a helpless drug addict that my pastor invited to church, a building project that I had to complete&amp;#8230; bizzare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>snowboarding!</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-12-31-128/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2004 01:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-12-31-128/</guid>
      <description>I would&amp;#8217;ve liked to say that my first experience snowboarding was overwhelming fun, with me sliding smoothly to the bottom of the mountain (just like SSX3!) as pictured below:
However, it was not to be. Not that it wasn&amp;#8217;t immensely fun, but my experience looked more like this:
Yes indeed. I must have fallen at least sixty times, with twenty-five of those times in the first run down. I spent the majority of my time on mt rear end, and needless to say, my post snowboarding pain was very great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-12-24-127/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2004 23:52:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-12-24-127/</guid>
      <description>&amp;#8217;twas the night before Christmas and up in the air
flew a little blue man draped in silky black hair
He spouted his wisdom, and told all his jokes
But he did this in silence, lest he wake other folk
His tired companion curled up in her seat
Dreams of snow-covered hills, a wonderful treat!
As they both closed their eyes, a well deserved rest
A loud voice they heard, shouting with zest</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>here we are again..</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-12-20-126/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2004 18:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-12-20-126/</guid>
      <description>&amp;#8230; at the end of another term. I&amp;#8217;ve been here before, at the end of a work term, and yet I haven&amp;#8217;t. Not like this. The milestones that I had set up have all been reached, and I feel a bit confused as to where to go from here. So much looks the same, and yet so much has changed. My mind, thoughts, and schedule have all been flipped on their heads, spun around, tossed into the air, and thrown back into the spots that they were in, looking for all the world like nothing happened to them, yet with their innards still whirling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>introspect</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-11-23-124/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2004 01:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-11-23-124/</guid>
      <description>Over the past few days/weeks/months, I&amp;#8217;ve been thinking about my future. It&amp;#8217;s just dawned on me that my stint in University is just about finished. Just when you think you know all the tricks, you&amp;#8217;ve figured out your place in the world&amp;#8230; you&amp;#8217;re rudely ejected from the seat you&amp;#8217;ve been sitting in for four or five years. Some try to climb back in, taking years of graduate studies&amp;#8230; but I don&amp;#8217;t think that&amp;#8217;s for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>addendum</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-11-01-123/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2004 20:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-11-01-123/</guid>
      <description>more photos:
The racoons in Stanley Park were incredibly friendly:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the wonder of it all</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-10-29-122/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2004 04:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-10-29-122/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, I was treated to an evening at the Vancouver Aquarium, where they had set up tables of food around near each station. As you stood in line waiting for food, you could look at all the different sea creatures around. I must say that I was impressed by this attraction. There were so many interesting things to look at, and there was a live band playing, causing many of the conference attendees to spontaneously dance!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>oopsla</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-10-26-121/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2004 23:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-10-26-121/</guid>
      <description>So for those of you who haven&amp;#8217;t guessed yet, I&amp;#8217;m not in Toronto anymore. I&amp;#8217;ve been given permission by my company to go to OOPSLA, all expenses paid! =)
 
The conference is held in the Vancouver Convention and Exhibition Centre
OOPSLA is a conference put on by the ACM, and it&amp;#8217;s been a great learning experience. I had a chat yesterday with the lead architect for the two Mars Rover Landers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>food blog 4 &amp;#8211; Monday, October 25, 2004</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-10-25-120/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2004 22:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-10-25-120/</guid>
      <description>Restaurant &amp;#8211; VCEC (Conference Location)
Type &amp;#8211; Breakfast
Meal &amp;#8211; Continental Breakfast (free)
Good croissants, but orange juice in wineglasses? Weird.
Restaurant &amp;#8211; Kareiko Japanese (Burrard St, Vancouver)
Type &amp;#8211; Lunch
Meal &amp;#8211; Bento ($14.50)
Excellent sashimi! A bit on the pricey side, but definitely upper class atmosphere. The only Japanese restaurant that I&amp;#8217;ve ever been to where the waiters/chefs all spoke Japanese exclusively to each other. This was quite possibly the most stylish bento I&amp;#8217;ve ever had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>thanks guys</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-10-22-116/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2004 00:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-10-22-116/</guid>
      <description>In regards to my previous post, thanks for everyone who encouraged me. =) We&amp;#8217;ll see how it goes&amp;#8230; Guess I&amp;#8217;ll just keep praying. Anyhoo, I wanted to talk today about sarcasm. Who thinks I&amp;#8217;m sarcastic, raise your hand! Why am I sarcastic? I don&amp;#8217;t know. Maybe I&amp;#8217;ll figure it out sometime. Oh well, I&amp;#8217;ll have my flick-er back, and flicking will commence soon. Very soon. Yes, this post was nonsensical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>restless</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-10-16-115/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2004 01:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-10-16-115/</guid>
      <description>Well, today was an interesting time at fellowship. The whole time there, I couldn&amp;#8217;t sit still, and I know that I wasn&amp;#8217;t being very helpful to the discussion. Usually, what calms me down is the singspiration. The singing, the music, and the praise all helps me to focus on God and to prepare my mind for learning. However, now that I have been pushed into the position of singspiration leader, singspiration has turned from a source of relaxation and calm to a source of anguish and anxiety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>limbo</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-10-15-114/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2004 14:52:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-10-15-114/</guid>
      <description>sigh. Still don&amp;#8217;t know the date of my midterm yet. It is incredibly difficult to take a course intended for the classroom via distance education. Not so much the lectures as the fact that you can&amp;#8217;t ask for help. =( Admitedly, the assignments aren&amp;#8217;t that hard, but there is no verification or checking of answers, that is typical when you are in school. Anyway, the newsgroup is almost empty of posts and I am getting worried.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sleepless in TO</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-09-29-113/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2004 02:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-09-29-113/</guid>
      <description>Again, I find myself unable to find solace in the soft blankets of my comfy bed,but this time because I am too excited about something. I can&amp;#8217;t tell you what it is, but I can tell you about my weekend. =) It started off with me leading worship for fellowship, a pitiable rendition of &amp;#8220;House of the Lord&amp;#8221; (the only song I know how to play on guitar), but we had a good bible study nonetheless on the parable of the Talents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trolling</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-09-24-112/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2004 14:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-09-24-112/</guid>
      <description>Last work term, I took a course about propositional and computational logic, CS245. The course itself was fairly interesting and moderately useful (especially for straightening out complex IF statements!) but the most interesting occurence happened near the end of term, on a newsgroup. If you didn&amp;#8217;t know, UW supplies newsgroups for courses to allow for discussion of class material, assignment clarification, and questions for TAs. When used correctly, they provide a great forum to discuss ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>i got in!</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-09-18-111/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2004 01:09:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-09-18-111/</guid>
      <description>So it seems I&amp;#8217;m going to be taking Databases &amp;#8220;Distance Ed&amp;#8221; next term&amp;#8230; crazy! =) I need to be disciplined&amp;#8230; sigh. In other news, I have a dilemma&amp;#8230; I need to lead worship next next week, but I also need to go to waterloo for saturday&amp;#8230; what to do! =/ This requires much ponderance. Oh, and since I&amp;#8217;ve joined extreme fitness, that also requires a whole other level of discipline&amp;#8230; working out four times a week will probably sap a lot of my strength.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the working man</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-08-30-109/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2004 17:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-08-30-109/</guid>
      <description>First day of work, and it&amp;#8217;s been interesting&amp;#8230; catching up with all the people here. Everyone went on vacation, so they&amp;#8217;ve got lots of stories to tell! I have my nice workstation back, and I never knew how much I missed dual monitor until today! =) I still have all my old programs on here, everything&amp;#8217;s designed to make my life easier. =) I even managed to get ICQ working, and it only took me 2-3 hours!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>psycho</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-08-17-108/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2004 18:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-08-17-108/</guid>
      <description>I was looking through my shelf for things to throw out, and I found a book of my writings from 1995. I had forgotten all about this, but my dad went through this phase where he wanted me to stop reading so many books, so he made me write a report on every single book that I wanted to read. I think this is why I hated writing for so much of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>it&amp;#8217;s coming&amp;#8230;</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-08-05-107/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2004 00:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-08-05-107/</guid>
      <description>*insert evil laughter here*
(there was an image of a tracking form here, but I removed it cause it was taking up space)
update! It&amp;#8217;s here!! =)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>perfect day</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-07-24-106/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2004 21:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-07-24-106/</guid>
      <description>Today was an absolutely gorgeous day! 23 degrees, sun shining brightly, nice and breezy&amp;#8230; what more could I ask for? except that I woke up at 2:30 pm, cause I&amp;#8217;m an idiot. Anyway, played tennis today from 4 pm till 6 pm, came home. Then I saw the open swimming pool and did a few laps in it. Yes, I swam in the westcourt swimming pool. Water clarity was a bit lacking, and there were bits and pieces of things lying around, but there was nothing living in the pool, thank goodness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>blood donation count&#43;&#43;</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-07-15-105/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2004 23:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-07-15-105/</guid>
      <description>So a few days ago, I&amp;#8217;m over at SLC giving blood for my second time. As the nurse is trying to draw blood, I&amp;#8217;m talking to my friend, and all of a sudden I stop talking. My friend asks me what&amp;#8217;s wrong, and I answer that I am extreme pain&amp;#8230; the nurse is pulling and pushing the needle back and forth, and she does this five or six times trying to find a vein!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sleepless in waterloo</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-06-13-103/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2004 01:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-06-13-103/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;#8217;t sleep. Not because I have any things of great import on my mind, but because I took a nap earlier on Waiki&amp;#8217;s couch to the sounds of Team Fortress Classic. Anyway, today was a busy day, with sports taking up the majority of it. Three hours of badminton coupled with two hours of tennis makes for a really tired and aching body. At least I can burn away some of this evil fatness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>culinary arts</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-05-21-102/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2004 14:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-05-21-102/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve been having some fun this term whipping up random things for lunch or dinner. I guess my biggest problem has been that most of the stuff I make looks good, smells good, but ends up tasting rather bland. For example, my pasta sauce, my chasiu-omelete, and my bizzare stewed veal mix with carrots all tasted rather bland. Well, I just discovered that time does make a difference. =) a little marination, a little udon goodness, and we can turn out something like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Imperial Oil</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-05-18-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2004 02:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-05-18-101/</guid>
      <description>Before anyone asks, I had NO ulterior motives in volunteering for this thing. =p Anyway, last week I volunteered as a teaching assistant for the Imperial Oil Seminar in Computer Science for Young Women. I really had a blast, especially since one of my favourite things in the world to do is teach! It was really incredible working with bright young minds that were really honest-to-goodness willing to learn! In fact, one of my favourite students was so keen to learn that even though she selected the hardware lab option, (you had a choice between programming and hardware) she borrowed the lab book for programming and tried to work through it on her own!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>update</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-04-22-100/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2004 15:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-04-22-100/</guid>
      <description>oh, goodness&amp;#8230; it&amp;#8217;s been so long since I posted that my last post has expired already. I promise to get something up soon&amp;#8230; it&amp;#8217;s just that it&amp;#8217;s the end of term, where everything&amp;#8217;s wrapping up. sigh. As a side note, I got a 20.1&amp;#8243; LCD monitor. mmmmmmm&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230; =)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>echos of the mind</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-03-26-99/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2004 00:18:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-03-26-99/</guid>
      <description>I was reading some fantasy today, and I picked up the new Robert Jordan hardcover for 40% off, thanks to Sarah&amp;#8217;s iRewards card. =) Anyway, I was just thinking about the reading I was doing and the way the character&amp;#8217;s voices sound in my head. A lot of the time, they sound like various people I know, who have similar characters. Apparently, hearing voices in your head makes your reading slower (actually, it&amp;#8217;s also a sign of impending lunacy) but I feel that it adds to the effect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IM and social interactions</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-03-09-98/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2004 14:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-03-09-98/</guid>
      <description>The explosion of IM (Instant Messaging) has been met with trepidation by those born before the internet revolution, and enthusiasm by those who have experienced its utility. There is no denying that IM is gaining a massive user base; in 2002, the number of active total IM users across the board (AIM, MSN, Yahoo, ICQ) hit 41 million. However, an entire generation is growing up with IM as their primary form of communication, and this may impact face-to-face and telephone conversations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>engine upgrade</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-02-26-97/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2004 17:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-02-26-97/</guid>
      <description>It seems that the blogosphere is getting more and more high tech&amp;#8230; from technorati, which tracks your online &amp;#8220;cosmos&amp;#8221; (inbound and outbound blog links) to rss feeds (which I have recently repaired and made availiable for this site here), technology, both necessary and unnecessary has been exploding within the blogging community. The latest fad to hit the blogging scene is trackback, which allows you to essentially remotely post comments on other people&amp;#8217;s website, in the form of a blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>spending time with kids</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-02-24-96/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2004 14:27:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-02-24-96/</guid>
      <description>As I was traversing the net today, I came across the following article:
&amp;#8220;Research shows that children under the age of eight are unable to critically comprehend televised advertising messages and are prone to accept advertiser messages as truthful, accurate and unbiased. This can lead to unhealthy eating habits as evidenced by today&amp;#8217;s youth obesity epidemic. For these reasons, a task force of the American Psychological Association (APA) is recommending that advertising targeting children under the age of eight be restricted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>role reversal</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-02-11-95/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2004 00:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-02-11-95/</guid>
      <description>For the first time, today, I got to sit on the other end of the table, taking on the role of the interviewer. Suprising how many students didn&amp;#8217;t realise that I was another co-op&amp;#8230; =) Anyway, I should elaborate. I went with a full-timer and another co-op up to Waterloo today, to interview some students for my current position. It was a fascinating experience, and I learned a lot about what not to do during an interview:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Le Concert de Feu</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-02-01-94/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2004 21:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-02-01-94/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve decided to really get to know my city this term, rather than do what I&amp;#8217;ve been doing in previous terms, which mainly consists of sitting and wasting time in my room every day. Tonite I went to a spectacular display of fireworks and drumming skill. I mean these guys were amazing&amp;#8230; they were Les Commandos Percu, which translates as &amp;#8220;the striking commandos&amp;#8221;, and strike they did. Their intensity in drumming was matched only by the awe-inspiring display above them, perfectly timed fireworks, in a dazzling display, delighting both eyes and ears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>puck &amp;#8211;&amp;gt; net</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-01-28-93/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2004 00:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-01-28-93/</guid>
      <description>Today, I went to the second Toronto athletic event of my life&amp;#8230;. box tickets, for the Leafs game. As Daniel will readily attest, I know next to nothing about hockey. Why is it that everytime I go to a game, I get awesome seats and know nothing about the game? I thought it was no more complicated than sending the ball/puck/cylinder/miscellaneous object into the net/basket/hole/bowl, but apparently there are some deep nuances or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OTPP</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-01-21-92/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2004 16:09:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-01-21-92/</guid>
      <description>As some of you know, I&amp;#8217;ve started working at the Ontario Teacher&amp;#8217;s Pension Plan. Apparently the most commonly known fact about this company is that they own the Toronto Maple Leafs. *shrug* I didn&amp;#8217;t know that when I started. However, there is no denying that they have money, and lots of it. I mean, I just got back from a conference in Hockley Valley, where the estimated cost of staying is $250 / night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Urbana pt. 5 &amp;#8211; Commitments</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-01-15-91/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2004 21:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-01-15-91/</guid>
      <description>Just when you thought it was over. =)
Everyone at Urbana filled out a decision card, basically highlighting and emphasising the commitments that people made during Urbana. This was done to serve as a reminder after the event was over. This is what I committed to do at Urbana:

 allow God to reign over my life, and to obey God&amp;#8217;s willl as taught in the Bible.
 renounce my idols, including my sense of entitlement</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Urbana pt. 4 &amp;#8211; Christian Community</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-01-04-90/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2004 22:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-01-04-90/</guid>
      <description>Even in an enormous campus like the University of illinois, the effect of twenty thousand Christians was immediately apparent. No matter where you looked, there were people praying, preaching, and reading bibles. Morning hours were filled with people praying and doing devotions, anxiously awaiting word from their God. Forgetting was impossible, as reminders were all around. Prayers were common, and praises even more so. Hallways would echo with personal songs sung directly to God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Urbana pt. 3</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-01-03-89/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2004 23:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-01-03-89/</guid>
      <description>The campus of Urbana, Illinois is simply a gorgeous sight. Wherever you walk, you&amp;#8217;re surrounded by green fields, and amazing buildings. I&amp;#8217;ve posted a few photos in the gallery for your viewing pleasure. I&amp;#8217;ve got higher quality images, so let me know if you want printable/backgroundable images. The experience of worshipping with 19,674 other Christians was unbelievable. Corporate prayer on its own is amazing, but hearing prayers to God echo in a thundering roar almost moved me to tears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Urbana pt. 2</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2004-01-02-88/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2004 02:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2004-01-02-88/</guid>
      <description>Going into Urbana, I thought that I would spend the majority of my time learning about small groups, and fellowships, and practical knowledge like that. Maybe some good worship sessions, a lot of singing, nothing too life-changing. Instead, God brought me face to face with Him, and His light just illumined all the idols that were in place between me and him. From entitlement and materialism to pride and relationships, God showed me a lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>christmas</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-12-23-86/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2003 03:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-12-23-86/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve been back for 5 days, and I&amp;#8217;m still cleaning! So much to move, so much to unpack! I&amp;#8217;m just glad that I&amp;#8217;ve finally cleared out most of the upstairs hallway, so most of my junk is in my room (yay!). I can&amp;#8217;t see my floor anymore, and to get into bed I have to vault over a veritable mountain of stuff. My mom tells me that people are coming over soon, so I have to get everything cleaned, so that&amp;#8217;s what I&amp;#8217;ve been doing till 4 am every morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gadgetry</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-12-20-85/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2003 03:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-12-20-85/</guid>
      <description>For those of you who haven&amp;#8217;t seen my room, this is what it looks like:
Now, those of you who know me well enough to know what I do and do not own, There is one thing that is out of place here.
That&amp;#8217;s right, you guessed it&amp;#8230; I only have ONE laptop. And yet, no, your eyes do not decieve you, for there on my ghetto makeshift desk is a SECOND laptop&amp;#8230; That&amp;#8217;s right, an Inspiron 8600 to be exact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&amp;#8230;and I&amp;#8217;m back</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-12-18-84/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2003 01:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-12-18-84/</guid>
      <description>Well, after a grueling ordeal of three difficult exams (see agk&amp;#8217;s site for more information on cs 341) and an even more exhausting move, packing up everything I&amp;#8217;ve acquired in four months of travel (which is more than I can say, thanks mostly to b.p., I am back in Toronto, all set for another work term. The main difficulty in adjusting to life in Toronto is that you essentially acquire two (or more) new housemates, except that they are a much higher &amp;#8220;rank&amp;#8221; than you, and think they know you inside out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stalker</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-12-09-83/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2003 02:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-12-09-83/</guid>
      <description>Setting: forest path leadaing from UW to Westmount and University
A dark night, and two students, walking quietly home, after a full day of studying. Even the full moon&amp;#8217;s light was drowned out by the branches of the forest. They whispered in hushed voices, conversing of the days events, planning the next day of studying. Quiet whispers that boomed like shouts across the silent path. A hooded man caught sight of the pair, and began to walk faster for a better look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>mobile</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-12-08-82/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2003 22:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-12-08-82/</guid>
      <description>As some of you know, I got a new axim a few days ago&amp;#8230;. It&amp;#8217;s a wonderful toy, and I&amp;#8217;ve been having a lot of fun with it. It&amp;#8217;s equipped w/ 802.11b (wireless) meaning I can use icq/msn at school! I&amp;#8217;m currently making this post on my axim from MC!
Anyway, I&amp;#8217;ve been really busy w/ studying lately, so nothing too eventful. My laptop broke again, though, so I sent an email to Michael Dell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>buried alive!</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-11-20-81/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2003 19:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-11-20-81/</guid>
      <description>Work is starting to overload. Wait, did I say starting? I meant continuing. I have to do a ton of UML sequence diagrams, and there&amp;#8217;s no end in sight. I had to forgoe the celebration of my cousin&amp;#8217;s birthday this saturday to do OS/Algorithms, and that&amp;#8217;s just not cool. I haven&amp;#8217;t been back in months! I hope they haven&amp;#8217;t forgotten me&amp;#8230; haha. They might, you know. Out of sight, out of mind?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>from the sheepfold</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-11-11-80/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2003 17:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-11-11-80/</guid>
      <description>We remember those who dedicated their lives in the wars, and those who were born on this day of remembrance:
May your day be truly blessed by the Creator of all life!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>47 hours to the minute</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-11-10-78/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2003 12:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-11-10-78/</guid>
      <description>login: j34wong
password: ***
Welcome to the UW CS servers!
bash$ cs350_submit
&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;done!
bash$ cvs commit project
&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;done!
bash$ cvs commit time
&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;.error, disk space full!
bash$ cvs commit brain
&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;.error, file is corrupt, please try again.
bash$ cvs commit brain
&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;error, corrupted memory segment
&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;SysCall(Terminate brain)
&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;&amp;#8230;internal framentation error, system going down for reboot</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>slice of my mind</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-10-29-77/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2003 19:43:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-10-29-77/</guid>
      <description>since I haven&amp;#8217;t posted in a looooong time, here&amp;#8217;re two posts, this one far less serious than the last one. I realised again today how mo liu my thought pattern goes. Here&amp;#8217;s what I was thinking about as I was walking home just now: the word propulsion. The root of it is &amp;#8220;propel&amp;#8221;, yet there is a noun version of of that doesn&amp;#8217;t contain some of the root. I was trying to think of as many as I could, but this is as far as I got, and maybe you can help!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>slacker</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-10-28-76/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2003 02:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-10-28-76/</guid>
      <description>I recently told a friend that your identity isn&amp;#8217;t something you discover, as if it&amp;#8217;s ingrained within you. It&amp;#8217;s established. You can determine who or what you want to be. I was doing some self examination, looking at the past few months, and I&amp;#8217;ve noticed that I&amp;#8217;ve become a real slacker, as Sam would say. =) Sleeping in, staying up late, not studying enough&amp;#8230; these are just a few of the things I hope to change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>backlash</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-10-06-75/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2003 02:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-10-06-75/</guid>
      <description>&amp;#8220;Above all else, guard your heart, for it is the wellspring of life.&amp;#8221; &amp;#8211; Proverbs 4:23
I first heard this verse four years ago, and I&amp;#8217;ve never forgotten it since. At first glance, this verse looks to be referring to things coming in, like thoughts, desires, and feelings. However, I&amp;#8217;ve been thinking lately, that it&amp;#8217;s important to watch what comes out of the heart. After all, the tongue is merely the expression of what the heart feels, so my words should be clean too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>attachment patterns</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-10-02-74/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2003 11:38:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-10-02-74/</guid>
      <description>So, I&amp;#8217;m learning about how people are attached to their peers in my psych class, and I come across these three:
securely attached: I find it relatively easy to get close to others and I am comfortable depending on them and having them depend on me. I don&amp;#8217;t often worry about being abandoned or about someone getting to close to me.
anxiously attached: I find that others are reluctant to get as close as I would like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>screwed</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-10-01-73/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2003 01:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-10-01-73/</guid>
      <description>ever get the feeling that just around the corner, there&amp;#8217;s something unknown, just around the corner, waiting to jump out and screw you? Well, I discovered what it was today&amp;#8230; my psych 354 midterm, in two days. That, coupled with a (thus far) solo OS project, an untouched software spec assignment, and an evening-wasting algorithms assignment (took out three hours with nothing to show for it), makes for a very depressing academic career so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>serenaded</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-09-19-72/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2003 12:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-09-19-72/</guid>
      <description>I think one of the best ways to be woken up is to have someone sing you awake. I mean, wouldn&amp;#8217;t it be amazing to be serenaded awake every day? That would be the best alarm clock ever! Well, today I was awoken (albeit unintentionally) by someone singing. It turned out to be Jasy practicing for her audition, but still, it was enjoyable. =) She was singing &amp;#8220;His Eye is on the Sparrow&amp;#8221;, a really touching song that I first heard at KWCAC, sung by Clara.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>public class CS341 implements boredom {</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-09-12-71/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2003 01:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-09-12-71/</guid>
      <description>Since I&amp;#8217;m writing this from within my class, you can tell that I&amp;#8217;m really bored. Anyhow, the first week is almost over, and it&amp;#8217;s been packed with events! Last night, Waiki invited a ton of people over for dinner, and it was lots of fun&amp;#8230; especially the game of Balderdash that occured after! Some of Andrew&amp;#8217;s definitions&amp;#8230; *sigh*
Anyway, last night I got to plan out the cell group that I&amp;#8217;m co-leading with my co-lead, JH.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>as it ends, so it begins</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-09-06-70/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2003 23:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-09-06-70/</guid>
      <description>I find myself thinking in this last day before the school term starts in earnest. This past week has been more a part of summer holidays than a part of school. It&amp;#8217;s been so much fun, hanging around, and doing what amounts to nothing, but I worry about my coming term. A very difficult and time-consuming term lies ahead, and I hope and pray that I can use my time wisely to both further God&amp;#8217;s kingdom, and improve my academic performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vacation!</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-08-27-69/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2003 01:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-08-27-69/</guid>
      <description>My first week of vacation hasn&amp;#8217;t been very productive&amp;#8230; Although I&amp;#8217;ve managed to finish 1 (only 1!!) book, I&amp;#8217;ve done little else. Church gave a nice gift of a $15 gift card at staples for volunteering at the summer camp. That&amp;#8217;ll buy some school supplies! =) Today, I went shopping with my mom&amp;#8230; looking for nothing in particular, just spending time before school starts again. My brother and sister are away on retreat, so there&amp;#8217;re three in in the family right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>answered prayer</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-08-20-68/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2003 00:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-08-20-68/</guid>
      <description>Praise God! Statistics 231 has been completed, and not a mercy pass! I am SO happy&amp;#8230; seriously, the only thing stopping me from running around outside the street yelling is that I already showered. Such a blessing! I was really really scared about this mark. I even talked to my prof! The exam was just brutalising. I feel like a huge load has been lifted off me! =) I&amp;#8217;ll still keep to my promise to reduce distraction, though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>photos of vbs are up!</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-08-15-67/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2003 17:48:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-08-15-67/</guid>
      <description>Well, the photos of VBS have been posted, although they are a bit big. Some of them are still in RAW format, so I have to convert it. Anyway, the power outage caught us seconds after the end of VBS on Thursday, making it next to impossible to see in the basement. I talked to a director, asking to move the kids upstairs/outside, to be picked up, but instead, we moved ALL the children into a tiny, narrow corridor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>what a day!</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-08-14-66/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2003 04:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-08-14-66/</guid>
      <description>I actually intended to post yesterday, but I slept for a loooooooong time&amp;#8230; and so I&amp;#8217;m late, but anyway:
The past two days have been hectic, from the massive chaos of moving out (despite only moving two blocks) to g.y.&amp;#8217;s surprise birthday party serenade. =) But anyway, I shall start from the beginning.
It all started on Monday, when I began to move out of my house, intending to leave for Toronto at 2pm on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>okay..</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-08-10-65/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2003 01:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-08-10-65/</guid>
      <description>I just re-read my post, and realised that it was more than slightly melodramatic. =P Then again, I had just finished writing it, so I guess I had a right to be a bit upset. =) Anyhow, I feel better now, especially after the wedding I attended today. =) Jack Wong, my conductor, and Cass Leung, a friend from church, got MARRIED today! =) Weddings are always so happy&amp;#8230; I love watching weddings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>finis</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-08-08-64/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2003 16:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-08-08-64/</guid>
      <description>As I exit the room of my final exam today, there is no sense of elation at having completed another school term, no sense of satisfaction. Instead, I only feel exhaustion, coupled with a growing sense of dread at the possibility of having to retake statistics. With next to no sleep, I head hope with a heavy heart. The only thing that gives me comfort is knowing that my success or failure rests entirely within the hands of God, as I have done the best I could in the little time I alotted for that course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>disconnected</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-08-05-63/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2003 14:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-08-05-63/</guid>
      <description>I feel really disconnected from school right now&amp;#8230; so many things can distract me. especially really cool things. I came across this page, teaching you how to write in elvish! I was bored, so I played around with it. Here&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8220;Joseph Wong&amp;#8221; in Tengwar cursive:
What fun! =)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>church</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-08-03-62/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2003 17:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-08-03-62/</guid>
      <description>led worship today&amp;#8230; recruited by mike around 6:30 pm, Saturday night, AGAIN! =p *sigh*
Oh well, everything turned out for the better. For those of you who were there, and noticed me trying not to laugh, (while on the stage, yes!) I was observing the antics of a two-year-old child, doing random, curious things. =) He kept playing with the thermostat, while his mother tried to hold his hands down, and walking away from his mom, into the aisles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>busy, busy, busy</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-08-02-61/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2003 13:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-08-02-61/</guid>
      <description>heh, you&amp;#8217;re all going to have to bear with me, as most of my next few posts will relate to school&amp;#8230; since I am embroiled in exams right now. =p
As for the exam I wrote yesterday night, one word.. BLEGH! I&amp;#8217;m glad it&amp;#8217;s over though&amp;#8230; it&amp;#8217;s highly probable that I will never have to take that course again, or anything that relates to it in any manner. =p Thanks to this professor&amp;#8217;s marking scheme and a cheat sheet policy, it&amp;#8217;s pretty difficult to fail this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>awake once more</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-07-30-60/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2003 10:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-07-30-60/</guid>
      <description>I just slept 13 hours, after falling asleep studying 342. And My stomache is reminding me that I haven&amp;#8217;t eaten in 15 hours. I&amp;#8217;m feeling awake ( a bit ), and the cs342 project is done, albeit with livelocking. =p Regardless, it is done, and I can spend the next 56 hours studying for 360, for which I feel woefully under-knowledged. *sigh*
It&amp;#8217;s hard to find a bright spot anywhere. I&amp;#8217;m sure there is one though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bloodless</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-07-22-59/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2003 22:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-07-22-59/</guid>
      <description>Mmm&amp;#8230;. i am now down 1&amp;frasl;2 a litre of blood. ON the plus side, I was up four oreos, two chocolate chip cookies, two and a half cups of apple juice, two pins, and sticker. I say &amp;#8216;was&amp;#8217;, because they&amp;#8217;re all gone now. =) Well, all except the pins and the sticker. Anyhow, before you all think that i was attacked by some giant mutant cookie-spitting, apple juice spewing mosquito, let me inform you that I gave up my blood voluntarily, unlike SOME people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tidbits</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-07-21-58/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2003 16:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-07-21-58/</guid>
      <description>Hah! I don&amp;#8217;t need em anymore&amp;#8230;. check this out! Been sitting in a lab all day trying to understand stats notes&amp;#8230; I&amp;#8217;m almost through chapter 7. I am soooo behind it&amp;#8217;s not funny. More on the picnic, it was at Shade&amp;#8217;s Mill, and there were no bugs around at all! Even though it took about 45 minutes to get the canoes because the attendant was sooooooo slooooooooooow, the canoeing trip was a fun excursion, especially the race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sore!</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-07-21-57/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2003 02:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-07-21-57/</guid>
      <description>A combination of canoeing, tug-o-war, and badminton, and sunburn has totally killed my arms and legs. This weekend was a blast though, even though i didn&amp;#8217;t do much work&amp;#8230;
Played a game of ghost with the high-schoolers from KWCAC, and everyone decided to gang up on me&amp;#8230;. I think they were just being sexist! =p Regardless, I had my share of good words, although when four people are trying to make you lose, its kind of difficult not to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>why we serve</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-07-14-56/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2003 23:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-07-14-56/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve been thinking a bit about why I do so much for ccf, why I serve as a bible study leader, or a cell group leader, or organize events like coffee house. As it happens, I was just reading 1 Peter, and I came across this verse in Ch.4 vs. 11: &amp;#8220;If anyone serves, let him serve with the strength God provides, so that in all things God may be praised through Jesus Christ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>neeeeeeeeeeeeeemmooooooooo</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-07-08-55/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2003 10:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-07-08-55/</guid>
      <description>I can talk in whale too. =) If you haven&amp;#8217;t watched the movie, you won&amp;#8217;t get the joke, and all I can say is &amp;#8220;Go watch it!&amp;#8221; It was the best movie I&amp;#8217;ve seen this whole term! Dory was so good, and the turtles were hilarious! The whale part just killed me&amp;#8230;. I was slapping my knee, and all. =) I couldn&amp;#8217;t stop laughing during the funny parts, and the heart-wrenching parts brought a tear to my eye (well, not literally).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hiatus</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-06-28-54/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2003 01:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-06-28-54/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;#8217;t written in awhile, have I? Well, I guess that&amp;#8217;s because I&amp;#8217;ve been pretty busy.. lots of things to accomplish. I started swimming recently. Haven&amp;#8217;t done that in&amp;#8230; oh&amp;#8230; four years? Totally kills my energy for the rest of the day. It feels good though! Even though I&amp;#8217;m getting my butt kicked by this other girl, who can swim non-stop. I have to take breaks every two lengths. I hope I get better soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>contented</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-06-19-53/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2003 13:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-06-19-53/</guid>
      <description>A gorgeous day outside, ice cream in my hand, and friends to walk with. =) What more could I ask for? Well, aside from a copy of my midterm tonite. =)
Other than that though, I&amp;#8217;ve never been more happy. This term has just been incredible so far, with so much to do, and so much more time to do it. I think that I&amp;#8217;ve learned a lot this term, and I&amp;#8217;m not talking about school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>curious</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-06-16-52/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2003 03:57:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-06-16-52/</guid>
      <description>the cat followed me into the bathroom. Why does the toilet seat not stay up? I am now talking to the cat. Concurrent operations. =)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lullaby</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-06-13-51/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2003 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-06-13-51/</guid>
      <description>&amp;#8220;Golden slumbers kiss your eyes
smiles await you when you rise&amp;#8221;
Thinking things through has never been my forte, and clearly, I was NOT thinking when I decided to set my &amp;#8220;alarm song&amp;#8221; (the one that plays to wake me up) to be Mozart&amp;#8217;s Lullaby. This was especially dumb, since the lyrics go like this: &amp;#8220;Go to sleep, go to sleep &amp;#8230;&amp;#8221; I heard that and I thought &amp;#8220;okay!&amp;#8221; and so didn&amp;#8217;t wake for another 2 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dance</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-06-10-50/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2003 02:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-06-10-50/</guid>
      <description>I noticed that a lot of my recent entries have to do with dancing. =) Who am I to break the pattern? hehehe
Anyhow, today was more dancing, intermediate social dance, and hip-hop performers. My feet hurt. A lot. I mean, the arch of my feet feels so pained that I think I&amp;#8217;d fall over if forced to walk for more than five minutes. Which is going to happen tomorrow, unless I take my bike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hip hop, reprise</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-06-05-49/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2003 02:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-06-05-49/</guid>
      <description>So, I&amp;#8217;ve been conscripted into the ranks of the CCF Coffee House hip-hop team. I am SO unsure of myself, it is not even funny. The performance is in TWO days! and I have another performance to practice for. I am sleep deprived, exhausted, and hungry. And yet life has never been more fun. =) I should&amp;#8217;ve given up games LONG ago. The amount of recovered time is incredible. One of my CS assignment is completely done, and the next one is started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&amp;#8230;5, 6, 7, 8!</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-05-29-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2003 16:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-05-29-48/</guid>
      <description>Heard throughout the UW Hip Hop club, of which I am now a member. That&amp;#8217;s pretty funny, at least to me, since I am one of the LEAST co-ordinated people I know. =) And yet, it was so much fun! The dance we were learning was pretty complicated, and my problem was that I couldn&amp;#8217;t think ahead. I always tell people I have a two-word queue in my head, (which means that when I say a word, I have two words planned after it), meaning that I suck at public speaking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dance_partner_count&amp;#8211;;</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-05-28-47/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2003 20:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-05-28-47/</guid>
      <description>So, yesterday, I&amp;#8217;m walkin&amp;#8217; to MC, extremely late for my cs class. I run into R, my current dance partner, sitting next to another guy, so I stop by to say hi. Then she introduces him as &amp;#8220;C, my boyfriend&amp;#8221;. At this point I&amp;#8217;m totally at a loss for words. I&amp;#8217;m trying to figure out what is going on, so I mumble something about being late for my class, and walk off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>justice</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-05-25-46/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2003 02:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-05-25-46/</guid>
      <description>I was thinking this past weekend, especially in light of recent events, about the issue of fairness. There&amp;#8217;s a lot of emphasis on &amp;#8220;giving people what they deserve&amp;#8221;, and there always has been. In fact, the oldest law in history is that of the &amp;#8220;eye for an eye&amp;#8221;. Even as Christians, we reward those deserving, and we punish those who are not. For example, this past friday night, we went to a resurant, and we recieved pretty bad service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>reloaded</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-05-15-45/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2003 01:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-05-15-45/</guid>
      <description>stop reading, if you haven&amp;#8217;t seen it. keep reading, if you don&amp;#8217;t care.
Okay, I just finished watching the second part of The Matrix, and, well, I dunno. Basically, it consisted of a bunch of long fight scenes, three to six important dialogue scenes (culminating in the final important dialogue scene), a bunch of irrelevant scenes, and then a whole bunch of scenes from the LAST matrix movie. There was some crazy revelations near the end, and a lot of people didn&amp;#8217;t really get it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>victory!!</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-05-14-44/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2003 10:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-05-14-44/</guid>
      <description>Couple updates: I have advance screening tickets to the Matrix Reloaded! 10:15 pm tonite, and I&amp;#8217;m going with a bunch of friends. We&amp;#8217;re going early to get good seats. hopefully it won&amp;#8217;t be too full! Secondly, I found a social dance partner! woooooo!
I&amp;#8217;ll be taking beginner again, since my partner isn&amp;#8217;t too keen on taking intermediate or advanced. =)
Anyhow, it&amp;#8217;s time for STATS! YAY!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>360</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-05-11-43/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2003 00:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-05-11-43/</guid>
      <description>Mamma Mia was awesome. =) Not quite as awesome as Lion King, but it&amp;#8217;s definately up there! The music was great, the vocals were great, the acting was good&amp;#8230; the only complaint I have was that some parts were a bit dirty. Nothing over 14A though, so it wasn&amp;#8217;t that bad. It was an interesting story, with a cool twist. I&amp;#8217;d go see it again, if I had the chance, if only for the ABBA songs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>blown away</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-05-04-41/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2003 18:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-05-04-41/</guid>
      <description>&amp;#8230;and I&amp;#8217;m not talking about some pansy leaf-in-wind blown away. I&amp;#8217;m talking 12 gauge shotgun to the chest kind of blown away. Words cannot describe yesterday&amp;#8217;s experience. I went to see Disney&amp;#8217;s The Lion King, and it was absolutely incredible. The human voice can convey so much emotion, and for some reason, whenever I hear a really incredible singer, my eyes start tearing up. I was almost wiping my eyes all through the performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gwar!</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-30-40/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2003 13:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-30-40/</guid>
      <description>Oh how I wish I had something to do&amp;#8230; it&amp;#8217;s gotten to the point where I&amp;#8217;m &amp;#8220;saving&amp;#8221; the time it takes to wash my dishes so that I can take up 10 minutes of my time here at work. =p On the plus side, I found a game with a VERY small screen-size footprint, so I can play it at work: SFCave! My high score has only been 2214, so if anyone can beat that, let me know!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>atwork</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-28-39/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2003 11:47:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-28-39/</guid>
      <description>final week of work&amp;#8230; only 5 days remaining. A sense of finality is in the air. Everything is completed. Work reports, outstanding projects, it&amp;#8217;s all done. I even cleaned up my desk! I&amp;#8217;m just waiting for it all to finish, so I can go back to school.
Worship on Sunday went fairly well, despite losing three core members, but Vic came in as a last minute replacement, saving the day! And Holz mad piano skillz also saved the day!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stalked</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-25-38/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2003 14:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-25-38/</guid>
      <description>no, this isn&amp;#8217;t about me stalking that camera guy. For my work report, I had to find out about a few pieces of software. one of them was called Verity UltraSeek. All I gave them was my email address. Somehow, he traced the domain, went to our website, called the company, and asked for me. the guy CALLED me!! and now he won&amp;#8217;t go away. He&amp;#8217;s bugging me incessantly, and I&amp;#8217;m getting very annoyed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>insanity</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-23-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2003 19:07:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-23-37/</guid>
      <description>This is how I looked by the end of the day.
I am DEAD for this weekend&amp;#8230; after an intense easter weekend, of over 25 hours at church, I am leading worship team 3 this Sunday. Jon, who was supposed to lead, is now in quarantine after he had a fever (which broke, so he&amp;#8217;s okay right now, and it&amp;#8217;s probably NOT SARS), leaving me to take over with a total of TWO other worship team members, since three others are unavailiable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chocolate</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-21-36/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2003 12:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-21-36/</guid>
      <description>There is SO much leftover chocolate at the office! I really should control myself, but it&amp;#8217;s soooooo good! It&amp;#8217;s not the super sweet, sugar-laced kind, it&amp;#8217;s the chocolatey goodness kind, and I&amp;#8217;m craving another piece as I type this, but I think I will not take anymore pieces. =p
Incidentally, the eBay camera guy said he shipped the camera, however, he has not provided a tracking number, even though there is insurance on the item.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tidbits</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-17-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2003 11:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-17-34/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m having difficulty selling the tungsten, altough I do have a promising offer from one guy for $490. We&amp;#8217;ll see how that pans out. =) The camera guy hasn&amp;#8217;t contacted me back yet, and if he hasn&amp;#8217;t by tonite, I&amp;#8217;m going to call him again. Using the net&amp;#8217;s resources, I have tracked down where he lives, and who his father is (and the fact that he&amp;#8217;s 51!) so I&amp;#8217;m pretty sure I can&amp;#8217;t get scammed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>easter</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-16-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2003 12:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-16-33/</guid>
      <description>On Monday, my cell group (minus Bonny) made easter eggs at my house! =) It was immensely fun, especially with the egg blowing and dyeing. My mom made &amp;#8220;dun dan&amp;#8221; (egg custard) with the remains of the egg, even though Leona had some saliva in her egg bowl. =p Ah well, boiling kills everything, right? hehehe.. Photos will be posted soon! Speaking of photos, my tungsten is due to arrive sometime today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tungsten t</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-10-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2003 19:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-10-32/</guid>
      <description>oh my shiny Palm
with photos and sound, tiny
you will be mine now
~joseph, 2003
Well, I&amp;#8217;ve finally decided on my treat for this term: A Palm Tungsten T, with a free 0.3 MP camera. Normally retailing for $599, I am getting this sweet item for $379. This&amp;#8217;ll satisfy my desire to take photos, as well as replace my broken clie. And it&amp;#8217;s SO small! It&amp;#8217;s quite amazing actually. I&amp;#8217;ll purchase it as soon as Dell releases the charge on my credit card for the Axims, which will happen in exactly three business days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>weekend</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-07-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2003 16:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-07-31/</guid>
      <description>Wow, the weekend was gorgeous! Not at all like the blizzard that is currently outside my window. =p It was so warm, in fact, that I was walking about in a t-shirt (yes, outside!) to shovel and clear my back patio. =) With my brother and sister, I made snow sculptures out of the remaining pieces of snow and ice, and we had a really fun time! I&amp;#8217;ll have photos up soon; now I REALLY want a digital camera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>female behaviour pt 2</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-03-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2003 14:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-03-30/</guid>
      <description>Here is our second installment of insight into female behaviour. Now, I know this won&amp;#8217;t apply to every female I know, heck, not even the majority of the females I know, but it&amp;#8217;s a pretty common thing; why high-heeled shoes? Where did they come from? After much searching about on the internet, I happened upon this website detailing the history of high heeled shoes. Essentially, high heeled shoes are a way for females to make up a height disadvantage, as well as forcing the muscles in the leg to be tensed, so that the calves are more shapely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>revelation</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-01-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2003 12:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-04-01-29/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve always wondered why females feel the need to go to the washroom in herds. At a nice dinner, or a prom or whatever, the instant a girl announces that she is going to the washroom, the entire female population at the table will get up and go with her. I&amp;#8217;ve always wondered why that was, and what they do in such a large group, with such small washrooms.
Anyways, yesterday, another secret of feminine hygiene was revealed to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>golf</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-31-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2003 16:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-31-28/</guid>
      <description>Went golfing over the weekend, for the first time! It was sooo much fun, but I&amp;#8217;m sore in so many strange places now. Muscles that I didn&amp;#8217;t even know existed are hurting now&amp;#8230; =( But it was worth it! I can hit the ball pretty far&amp;#8230; one of the most perfect shots I made nailed the golf-ball-collection truck dead on, way in the back of the tent. Now THAT was a sweet shot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>commitee</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-29-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2003 10:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-29-27/</guid>
      <description>well, after all that, I&amp;#8217;m not on the CCF commitee&amp;#8230; The spirit leads where He will, I guess. God has something else for me to do, it seems. I guess it&amp;#8217;s a good thing, since I can spend more time in prayer, and stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>resNet/housing competency</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-26-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2003 10:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-26-26/</guid>
      <description>Well, the short version is that complaining worked. =) Both Roger Watt (IST head) and Sheryl Skingly (Housing head) were most helpful, and now the blocked ports page carries a list of the degraded ports:
tcp 6112 dtspcd
udp 6112 dtspcd
udp 27005 &amp;#8211;
udp 27015 &amp;#8211;
So I guess that means no counterstrike or warcraft.. =(
Anyways, here is the response from Roger about the ports:
&amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;ve just extended http://noc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>resnet idiocy, pt 1</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-22-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2003 12:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-22-25/</guid>
      <description>Because I am living in Mackenzie King Village next term, I have to sign up for resNet, since there isn&amp;#8217;t an option and it&amp;#8217;s bundled into housing costs. I heard a rumour last term about certain ports, like 27015 and 6112 (for the uninitiated, counterstrike and battle.net) being blocked. This is unacceptable, so I decided to find out more. After emailing the resnet office, I was confronted with a guy who obviously had no idea what he was doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>resnet idiocy, pt 2</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-22-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2003 12:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-22-24/</guid>
      <description>&amp;#8212;&amp;#8211;Original Message&amp;#8212;&amp;#8211;
From: reshelp [mailto:reshelp@uwaterloo.ca]
Sent: March 21, 2003 12:30 PM
To: Joseph Wong
Subject: Re: resnet port blocking?
Hi there..ResNet is free to all residence students. Where you got 75 from is
confusing to me. I must warn you . We are very strict when it comes to
bandwidth usage and downloading of copyrighted material. If your cought you
will be disconnected. So if you need to use up loads of bandwidth were</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rss feed enabled</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-18-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2003 14:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-18-23/</guid>
      <description>I have fully enabled the RSS feed from this site. The address for it is: http://www.regularxpression.com/weblog/rss/rx.xml. As far as I know, it is working, so feel free to play with it. =) The RSS version is 2.0, and it should work fine for any viewers compatable with any of the .91/.92 versions.
and we&amp;#8217;re going to war. huzzah. but not us, which is good. =) Canada refuses to take part&amp;#8230;. wheeee!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>war</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-17-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2003 17:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-17-22/</guid>
      <description>Okay, I&amp;#8217;m sure a lot of people who are more qualified than me have talked about this, but I just have to say something. So the US is almost assuredly going to declare war tonite on iraq, because of supposed weapons of mass destruction, which we still have not seen concrete evidence of. And yet, here sits North Korea, thumbing its nose at the US, declaring that it has weapons of mass destruction, test firing missles every which way, basically saying &amp;#8220;screw you, UN, give us money cause we have nukes&amp;#8221; and yet the US (or anyone else for that matter, save South Korea) does nothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>random rants and updates</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-14-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2003 12:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-14-20/</guid>
      <description>Something that really annoys me is having people on my MSN list (icq doesn&amp;#8217;t seem to have this problem) with HUGE nicknames, in which they state anything from their life story, to their current thoughts, to their favourite colour of the minute. Why do people have this urge to write essays as their names? Nicknames are nothing more than identifiers, and it is impossible to IM people who either change their nicknames on an hourly basis, and/or use long paragraphs as their nicknames.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-11-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2003 14:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-11-19/</guid>
      <description>lifesong
one word. incredible. the stories shared on friday night really impacted me, and challenged the way that I think. I realized just how blessed I was when I was growing up, and I felt a renewed desire to help those less fortunate than me. My friends have gone through so much&amp;#8230; Marianne&amp;#8217;s song spoke to me, especially the line &amp;#8220;I will not try, I will rely&amp;#8221;. Those words rang very true, especially in this time when I have so many things to worry about, so many decisions to make.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-05-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2003 11:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-03-05-18/</guid>
      <description>the reason
There have been very few recent updates in part due to the horrible weather we&amp;#8217;ve been having, in part due to some actual work at work, and in part due to my own laziness. =P However, I&amp;#8217;ve managed to get in almost a full day of guitar practice on the weekend, and I can *almost* play &amp;#8220;God of Wonders&amp;#8221; straight through. =)
Anyways, I&amp;#8217;ve posted pictures of the tobogganing experience in the gallery, and I&amp;#8217;ll also talk about them here:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-27-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2003 14:22:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-27-17/</guid>
      <description>&amp;#60;?xml version=&amp;#8221;1.0&amp;#8243; encoding=&amp;#8221;ISO-8859-1&amp;#8243;?&amp;#62;
&amp;#60;blog:title=&amp;#8221;Today&amp;#8221;&amp;#62;
&amp;#60;rant&amp;#62;
I am so bored at work, I&amp;#8217;ve decided to change my bloggin&amp;#8217; stylez. Today&amp;#8217;s blog will be written in XML.&amp;#60;/rant&amp;#62;
&amp;#60;guitar&amp;#62;
After a few hours of practice yesterday, I finally managed to play the first verse of &amp;#8220;God of Wonders&amp;#8221;. Playing guitar is a LOT harder than I first thought, and it is even harder when you are teaching yourself. =P The main problem I have is strumming&amp;#8230; since I am not good at multi-tasking, fingering the notes and strumming in a decent pattern is currently beyond my abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-25-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2003 17:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-25-16/</guid>
      <description>frivolity
**Avril Lavigne &amp;#8211; Let Go &amp;#8211; $13.99 Bond &amp;#8211; Shine &amp;#8211; $16.99

After getting caught in a snowstorm and a huge traffic jam, I decided I would wait out the storm in Male Technology Paradise, Futureshop. =) Alright, I&amp;#8217;ll admit it, I was looking for the new Bond cd (four violinists, not James Bond. =P). While perusing the value section, I discovered the Avril Lavigne cd, conveniently low priced, and since I really like the quality of her voice, I picked it up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-19-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2003 15:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-19-14/</guid>
      <description>thoughts, not necessarily organized
I think that children today are hurting for a purpose, and this need is only intensified by our schools (which are supposed to give them something to strive for). For twelve years, hundreds of children are thrown together into a single building under the pretense of increasing their knowledge. In this time, school is to them what work is to us, a large chunk of their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-18-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2003 15:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-18-13/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;ve hacked together a thumbnail system for the photo gallery, so it looks a bit better now. Thanks to a liberal reuse of code the new system works just as well as the last one, with extra features.
annoyances
I am quickly getting tired of the problems that our subway system has. Today, it took me over 2 hours to get to work, thanks to a delay at eglinton&amp;#8230; However, I did get to try the new sheppard subway line, and I must say, it is very nice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-13-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2003 16:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-13-12/</guid>
      <description>In case you haven&amp;#8217;t noticed,  is now a top level domain, so update your bookmarks accordingly. Today has been pretty relaxed (as usual), and nothing eventful happened, aside from a pleasant surprise this morning on the ttc. It turns out that some of the eglinton 34 buses have upholstered seats! The only problem is, with seat dividers eliminated, it is difficult to isolate just where a seat ends and another begins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-12-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2003 15:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-12-11/</guid>
      <description>incompetence
So, at long last, I am able to get a new CPU from dell because of my warranty, and all because of one dell girl who had no idea what she was doing. Until today, I had never experienced the true horror of clueless tech support, and I even doubted its existance, but now I have firsthand experience of it. Throughout the entire support call, after every single thing I said, I got a &amp;#8220;hang on a sec?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-11-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2003 15:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-11-10/</guid>
      <description>The new archival system is online, although it is far from perfect. I haven&amp;#8217;t figured out how to disallow clicking on a date without a comment, but I&amp;#8217;m sure it shouldn&amp;#8217;t be too difficult. The good thing about it is that it limits the amount of entries displayed to those that were made the current week, so there is less displayed on the front page. As I was browsing about the web, I can across this article which analyzes the social hierarchy in weblogging, and how it follows a power law distribution (if weblogs are ranked according to inbound links).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-10-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2003 15:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-10-9/</guid>
      <description>elections
It&amp;#8217;s time for another FEDS election, and like last year, I have absolutely NO idea what is going on. I found out that the elections were going on from a friend who wanted me to vote for him. Anyhow, that got me interested into looking at the current issues in uw right now. Firstly, strikeable fees. I feel that this would be pretty convenient for me as a student, to get refunds for stuff that I don&amp;#8217;t pay for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-07-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2003 15:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-07-8/</guid>
      <description>the words we speak &amp;#8211; Eph 4
This afternoon, a friend sent me a bible study that he had written. It hit me so hard that I just had to write about it. It talked about how we should &amp;#8220;not let any unwholesome talk come out of [our] mouths&amp;#8221;. I had read this before, but as I thought about the words that I speak, I noticed that they are not always as pure or &amp;#8220;helpful for building others up&amp;#8221; as they should be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-06-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2003 15:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-06-7/</guid>
      <description>american idol
I was watching american idol yesterday, and I will have to admit, I am a fan of the show. Kimberly was not allowed to proceed, even though it looked like she was going to (she&amp;#8217;s very pretty), and I was very disappointed. I still can&amp;#8217;t get over how nice Kimberly was&amp;#8230; even after losing, she still went to encourage all the others, and keep a smile on.. I don&amp;#8217;t know if I&amp;#8217;d be able to do that, after losing a competition like that, it&amp;#8217;s just so incredible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-05-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2003 15:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-02-05-6/</guid>
      <description>upgrade
Although there isn&amp;#8217;t a visible difference, this site has just undergone a massive overhaul. You may notice a little performance degradation, but that&amp;#8217;s because everything is being loaded from SQL Server now, allowing for HTML code in posts, and a whole host of neat features. =)
TCG
Our first meeting went well, and we got a chance to share about our goals, and our resolutions for the term. A lot of interesting suggestions for programs were given including skating, movie night, and Praying over Oranges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-01-30-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2003 10:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-01-30-3/</guid>
      <description>Alright, I just posted some pictures, and after all the trouble I went through with my scanner last night, I&amp;#8217;m REALLY interested in getting a Digital camera. =P Any suggestions, anyone?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-01-29-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2003 13:23:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-01-29-2/</guid>
      <description>Yay! I have secure-ish posting set up. This is much better than before, where anyone who knew the address to the posting page could make updates to my weblog. =P Now only *I* can post, and you all can&amp;#8217;t! Except that my hand now hurts so much that I can&amp;#8217;t type anymore. =P This is with my left hand only, cuz though my right hand is feeling a little better, I don&amp;#8217;t want to strain it&amp;#8230;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>carpal tunnel</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/2003-01-29-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2003 09:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/2003-01-29-1/</guid>
      <description>Alright, I&amp;#8217;ve just discovered that I have carpal tunnel syndrome.. Yay! =P I checked the symptoms, and I have ALL of them&amp;#8230; numbness, pain, and difficulty grasping objects. So now I installed a program called Break Reminder that will force me to take a 20 second break every 10 minutes. It&amp;#8217;s a pretty robust program, and I&amp;#8217;m quite enchanted with it. =) I think I&amp;#8217;ll install it at work. Anyhow, it&amp;#8217;s time for lunch!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>